Yep we are going to deep fry this and we are going to have a breading on it that is just going to taste great.
I will show you how to do it. First off this is calamari that has been cut we had it cut first and we are going to go ahead and use these.
I didn't drain them very well, I'm going to get a paper towel and get them a little dryer in there.
So our breading has salt, pepper, a little bit of garlic, and then we put a little bit of Italian seasoning so it gives it that extra kick.
You could put anything you want into it it could be something hot and spicy it is jsut whatever your taste is.
Okay so we are just going to throw some in here and I'm going to do this by hand instead of trying to use the utensils my kitchen, my food, my fingers.
So I'm going to put that like that this is flour and I threw a little bit of the pepper and salt in there and this is our breading this is a great dry batter it is just bread crumbs and breading that has just been made especially for this type of thing.
We are going to put it right there and then we are going ot do this one and this is just eggs this is just eggs right there just beat up to make it sticky.
Here we go alright so we would finish this up, up here.
I will these into the deep fryer and see how long it take to get them fry.
Clean off my fingers.
Okay we are goign to put these into the basket here.
Next segment we are going to do we are going to do something very interesting we are going to do some oysters.
So when we come with this we see how many minutes it took to cook it and when it is golden brown it is done and then we would start on the oysters for you.
Okay I think these are ready now they have been in here for 4 1/2 minutes we had the temperature up about 375 and it depends on your taste if you like them a little bit darker then you could leave them a little longer but really watch them.
Cause once they start to get really brown they go fast.
Alright here you go simple, easy, delicious, deep fried calamari.
Find your you special sauce and go dipping go eat it.
The next thing you see from us the next segment would be oysters deep fried in breading.